[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いろんな' read in word?",
        "answer": "Різноманітний"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たび' read in word?",
        "answer": "Подорож"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はっぱ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Листочок"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いけばな' read in word?",
        "answer": "Ікебана (мистецтво квітів)"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'やきいも' read in word?",
        "answer": "Смажений батат"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ようじ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Справи"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しゅくだい' read in word?",
        "answer": "Д,З"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たいへん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Жахіття"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'バスてい' read in word?",
        "answer": "Автобусна зупинка"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もんばん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Охоронець, вахта"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ならびます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Стояти у ряд"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'こくりつ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Національний"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たとえば' read in word?",
        "answer": "Наприклад"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'じゅぎょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Урок"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かんたん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Простий"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おかし' read in word?",
        "answer": "Солодощі"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'びっくり' read in word?",
        "answer": "Здивування"
    }
]